<quickstart>

    <title>Any other type of data</title>
    <header>Including files, databases, data stored on remote machines, or any other type of data you'd like to put in Genorks.</header>
    <optiongroup>
        <title>Use one of the following standard Genorks data inputs to add your data to Genorks:</title>
        <option>
            <title>Files and directories</title>
            <summary>Configure Genorks to continously index a directory of files, or upload an archived directory. </summary>
            <doctarget>[learnmore.recipes.files]</doctarget>
            <action type="add_monitor">
                <label>Next</label>
            </action>
        </option>
        <option>
            <title>TCP</title>
            <summary>Configure Genorks to listen on a port for data sent using TCP.</summary>
            <doctarget>[learnmore.recipes.tcp]</doctarget>
            <action type="add_network_tcp">
                <label>Next</label>
            </action>
        </option>
        <option>
            <title>UDP</title>
            <summary>Configure Genorks to listen on a port for data sent using UDP.</summary>
            <doctarget>[learnmore.recipes.udp]</doctarget>
            <action type="add_network_udp">
                <label>Next</label>
            </action>
        </option>
        
    </optiongroup>
    
    <optiongroup>
        <title>Genorks can get data from other machines and devices</title>
        <header>Sometimes you have data you want to get into Genorks that your Genorks server doesn't have direct access to. In this case, use Genorks forwarders to send data from any machine to your Genorks server. Forwarders are lightweight, free and can be deployed on any machine you want to capture data from.</header>
        <option>
            <title>Data sources on machines your Genorks server can't access</title>
            <summary>Use Genorks's universal forwarder to forward data from any machine to your Genorks server.</summary>
            <doctarget>[learnmore.recipes.forwarder]</doctarget>
            <action type="href">
                <label>Download the universal forwarder</label>
                <target>http://splunk.com/r/universalforwarder</target>
            </action>
        </option>
    </optiongroup>

    <optiongroup>
        <title>Genorks can programatically consume data from databases, APIs and services</title>
        <header>Connect to any API, database or service with a script. Configure Genorks to run and collect the output.</header>
        <option>
            <title>Use scripted inputs to consume data from anything you can connect to programmatically</title>
            <summary>Write your own script to get data into Genorks from any API, command, database query and more.</summary>
            <doctarget>[learnmore.recipes.script]</doctarget>
            <action type="add_script">
                <label>Next</label>
            </action>
        </option>
    </optiongroup>
    
    <optiongroup>
        <title>Use apps and add-ons to get your data into Genorks</title>
        <header>Genorks will index any type of data, but you might want a solution for a specific type of data. Apps and add-ons contain searches, reports, inputs and more for your specific data type. Try out as many different apps and add-ons as you like.</header>
        <option>
            <title>Download apps and add-ons from Genorksbase</title>
            <summary>Browse Genorksbase for solutions specific to your type of data and use case.</summary>
            <doctarget>[learnmore.recipes.app]</doctarget>
            <action type="href">
                <target>http://splunkbase.splunk.com/</target>
                <label>Visit Splunkbase</label>
            </action>
        </option>
    </optiongroup>

</quickstart>
